https://haemophilia.org.uk/who-we-are/your-data-and-privacy/

Home » Who We Are » Data and privacy
Data and privacy
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy explains in detail the types of personal data we may collect about you when you interact with us. It also explains how we’ll store and handle that data, and keep it safe.
We know that there’s a lot of information here but we want you to be fully informed about your rights, and how The Haemophilia Society uses your data.
For example, we will explain things such as how we store and protect your data to build a picture of you.
We want everyone who supports us, or who comes to us for support, to feel confident and comfortable with how any personal information you share with us will be looked after or used. We hope the sections detailed in this policy will answer any questions you have but if not, please do get in touch with us at info@haemophilia.org.uk
You can read our full Privacy Policy here.
It’s likely that we’ll need to update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please do check back.
Recent Posts
Change to presentation shown at our Annual Member Conference
3 December 2020
Take Part in the Newly Launched National Bleeding Disorders Patient Experience Survey
2 December 2020
Joint statement from The Haemophilia Society and Healthcare at Home
30 November 2020
Popular Posts
Developments in Contaminated Blood Support January 2017
23 January 2017
Statement by the Board of Trustees of the Haemophilia Society on Contaminated Blood
28 March 2017
Update on the Contaminated Blood Support Schemes
21 September 2017
Categories
APPG
AWARENESS
CHARITY
EVENTS
020 7939 0780
Public Inquiry Media Information For all media inquiries connected with the Infected Blood Inquiry contact Jessica Bomford on 07973 407 011 or jessicab@haemophilia.org.uk
NEWSLETTER SIGN-UP
Sign up for more information on news, events and fundraising
Your shopping cart is empty.
Go to the shop
×
